我会去拿蜡烛跟我妈的蕾丝桌巾
So I'll get candles and my mom's lace table cloth.
因为我想让瑞秋过一个特别的生日
Since it's Rachel's birthday and we want it to be special...
我想我会做水煮鲑鱼      噢
I thought I'd poach a salmon        Oh
怎么了?
What?
问题是为什么每次办派对你都要做水煮食物?
Question, why do we always have to have parties where you poach things?
你要掌管食物委员会吗?
You wanna be in charge of the food committee?
问题二 为什么我们办派对一定要有委员会?
Question two, why do we always have parties with committees?
我们为什么就不能点些披萨...
Yeah, yeah. Why can't we just get some pizzas...
买几罐啤酒来狂欢?      对啊?
...and gets some beers and have fun?        Yeah.
我赞成派对真正好玩的地方是你打内心就喜欢它
Yeah, I agree.You know, I think fancy parties are only fun if you're fancy on the inside
但我不确定我们现在是不是
and I'm just not sure we are.
好吧 你们不希望它很特别
All right. You guys don't want it to be special
好吧 你们想办什么派对随便你们
Fine. You can throw any kind of party you want.
乔伊 它们不是真的      啊?啊?
Joey,they're not real.        Huh? Huh.
我在里面塞了很多东西 好么? 它们是假的
I start miles beneath the surface of these things, okay? They're fake.
看到没? 咔咔
See? Honk honk.
那像是给小丑看的色情片
Wow, it's like porno for clowns.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第22集
一个头两个大 The One With the Two Parties
调校制作：寒 枫
字幕编辑：恒星の恒心
我问过瑞秋的姐妹了 她们都来不了
I talked to Rachels sisters. Neither of them can come.
好吧 我还得要邀请戴伦 艾玛和莎朗古柏
Ok, so I still have to invite Dylan and Emma and Shannon Cooper.
喔 喔 喔 别邀请莎朗古柏
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Uh, no Shannon Cooper.
为什么?
Why not her?
因为她会偷东西
Because she, uh... She steals stuff.
或许她没偷东西 乔伊只是跟她上过床 没回她电话
Or maybe she doesn't steal stuff and Joey slept with her and never called her back.
乔伊 这太坑爹了吧
Joey, that is horrible.
我喜欢她 好吗? 或许我太喜欢她了 我也不清楚
Hey, I liked her,All right? Maybe may be too much. I don't know.
我想我只是被吓到了
I guess I just got scared.
天啊      抱歉 我不知道
oh        I'm sorry. I didn't know.
我以为没有人会相信 好吧
I didn't think anyone would buy that. Okay.
甜心 情况如何?      那是地狱般的毕业典礼
Hi, honey. How did it go?        Ugh. It was the graduation from hell.
我表弟可是靠足球奖学金才上那个"地狱大学"的
You know, my cousin went to hell on a football scholarship.
我是说那应该是个欢乐的场面
You know I mean this is supposed to be a joyous occasion.
我妹妹从大学毕业了 以前都没人想到她能毕业
My sister's graduating from college. Nobody thought she would.
应验了一句谚语 "会咬人的狗不会叫"
It's a true testament to what a girl from Long Island would do for a Celica.
发生了什么事?      是我爸妈啦
So, what happened?        My parents happened.
他们需要做的就是坐在同一个体育场骄傲地微笑
All they had to do was sit in the same stadium, smile proudly...
不再提离婚的事 但是他们却没能做到...
and not talk about the divorce. But no...
他们在毕业生致词时大吵一架
They got into a huge fight in the middle of the commencement address.
杜图主教不得不停下来嘘他们
Bishop Tutu actually had to stop and shush them.
但是你知道吗?你们知道好消息是什么吗?
Ugh. But you know what? You know what the good news is?
接下来我得端八小时的咖啡
I get to serve coffee for the next eight hours.
好吧 我想我们不能邀请她爸妈了
Okay, so I guess we don't invite her parents.
只邀请她妈妈怎么样?      为什么?
Well,how about just her mom?        Why her mom?
因为我已经邀请她了
Because I already invited her
你邀邀请史黛西・萝丝了吗?
did you ask Stacy Roth?
额...不能邀请她
Uh,can't invite her
她也会偷东西
She also steals.
这是生日蜡烛 生日蛋糕在哪里?
Okay, here are the candles. Where's the birthday cake?
没有生日蛋糕 我们要吃生日果馅饼
Okay,we're not having birthday cake. We're having birthday flan.
什么?
Excuse me?
那是传统墨西哥馅饼甜点      太棒了
It's a traditional Mexican custard dessert.        Whoa,that's nice.
生日快乐 瑞秋 吃点馅饼
Happy birthday, Rachel. Here's some go.
葛林医生
Dr. Green.
天啊 是瑞秋的爸爸
Oh, my God.It's Rachel's dad.
你来这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
什么?做父亲的不能在女儿过生日时来看她?
What?the father can't drop by to see the daughter on her birthday?
不 你当然可以啦
No. no. the father can.
我是她的室友 她现在不在这里
But, urn, since I am the roommate, I can tell you that she's not here.
我会告诉她的 好吗? 再见
And I'll pass along the message. Okay? So bye-bye.
你们在办派对呀
You're having a party.
不 不是派对
No, no, not a party.
只是一些认识瑞秋的人给她准备的惊喜聚会
Just a surprise gathering of some people Rachel knows.
他们是菲比 钱德跟乔伊      反正我也记不住
Uh, this is Phoebe and Chandler and Joey.        I'll never remember all of that.
那个惊喜是什么?
So, uh, what's the deal?
瑞秋一回家就会有人跳出来大叫? 是这样的吗?
Rachel comes home, people pop out and yell stuff? Is that it?
这不是你第一次参加惊喜派对吧?
This isn't your first surprise party, is it, sir?
你好 摩妮卡
Hi, Monica.
是中国餐馆的人 她忘了拿菜单
The Chinese menu guy. Forgot the menus.
其实只是一个中国人而已
So basically, just a Chinese guy.
葛林医生 请跟我来
Hey, Dr. Green. come with me.
我们得把你的外套放在瑞秋床上
We'll put your jacket on Rachel's bed.
好吧 听起来似乎是需要两个人才能做
All right. That sounds like a two-person job.
天啊 那是怎么一回事?
Well, my goodness. What was that?
桑德拉 我很抱歉 我以为你是瑞秋
Sandra, I am so sorry. I thought you were Rachel.
我们还没准备好瑞秋的派对
And we just weren't ready for you yet.
你以为我是瑞秋?      是啊 因为你看起来很年轻
You thought I was Rachel?        Yes, because, uh, you look so young.
因为你们都是白种女人
And because you're both, you know, white women.
孩子们 我想你们了 我该把外套放到卧室去吗?
Oh, I missed you kids.Well, should I put my coat in the bedroom?
不...
No...
不 我帮你放外套吧      谢谢
No,I'll take that for you.        Oh, well, thank you.
好的      你真是个绅士 谢谢
Okay.        Such a gentleman. Thank you.
哦
Oh.
看起来真漂亮呀 好多喜庆的气球啊
Oh, it all looks so nice. So festive all the balloons.
我来这里的路上发生了一件非常有趣的事
Oh,the funniest thing happened to me on the way here.
我开着车...      真好笑 哈哈哈
I was driving...        That's great. Ha-ha-ha.
我等不及要听完其他部分 但我得去上厕所
I can't wait to hear the rest, but I have to go to the bathroom.
那就跟我一起去吧      什么?
So,Hey, come with me.        what?
是呀 是呀 就当我们是好朋友
Yeah, yeah. It will be like we're gal pals
像在餐厅一样 一定会很好玩 来吧
You know, like at a restaurant. Oh it'll be fun. Come on.
哈哈 来吧
Ha, ha. Come on.
天啊...      快想想
Oh, my God,my God,my God.        Okay, think. Think.
杰克跟克丽丝会怎么做?
What would Jack and Chrissy do?
你的外套已经安全的放在床上了...
Okay, now that your coat is safely in the bed
我们可以回客厅了  哈哈
Okay. We can come back out in the living room. Ha ,Ha.
乔伊跟钱德 你们该带葛林医生去你们家
So, Joey and Chandler, I think it's time that you take Dr. Green over to your place.
当然
Uh, yes, absolutely.
为什么?
Urn, why, again?
因为派对要在那里举行 笨蛋
Because that's where the party is,you goon.
这里只是准备区
See, this is just the staging area.
对 这里是准备区      这里什么也没有
Right,it's the staging area.        There wasn't anything else
明显不是这个公寓
This is clearly in the wrong apartment.
好吧 你们去一号派对
All right, you guys are off to party number one.
你们...
And you...
你们去二号派对
You are off to party number two.
伙计们 动作快点...
All right, fellas, lets keep it moving, lets keep it moving.
钱德 拜托你能分一些女客人来参加我的派对吗?
Chandler, could you at least send some women to my party?
是罗斯 好吧
Okay,that's Ross. All right.
他们来了 嘘!
Okay,they're coming. Shh!
谢谢你请我吃晚餐
Thank you for such a wonderful dinner
谢谢这个世界有你存在
Thanks for being born.
谢谢你送我漂亮耳环 它们非常完美 我爱你
Oh,thank you for my beautiful earrings.They're perfect. I love you.
你不喜欢的话可以拿去换 好吗?
Oh. Now, you can exchange them if you want,okay?
现在我更爱你了
Hmm. Now I love you even more.
大惊喜!
Surprise!
天啊 摩妮卡
Oh, my gosh. Wow.Monica
天啊 妈 这真的是太棒了
Oh, my God. Mom.This is so great.
生日快乐  甜心
Happy birthday, sweetie.
是你 我都不知道
Wow. You.I had no idea.
真的吗?      不 我知道
Really?        No I knew.
好吧
All right.
大伙们 桌上有食物跟饮料
Everybody, there's food and drinks on the table.
快到对面       什么?
Go across the hall.        What?
到钱德跟乔伊家去 现在就去
Right now, Joey and Chandler's. Go.
为什么?      快去
Why?        Just go.
真奇怪      大惊喜!
Weird.        Surprise!
生日快乐 宝贝女儿
Happy birthday, sweet pea.
爸爸
Daddy! Ha,Ha.
他们都来了? 他们都来了?
Both of them are here? Both of them? Both of them are here?
我们可以再数一次
Well, we could count again.
我不敢相信会发生这种事
I can't believe this is happening
你知道吗? 这太荒谬了
You know what? This is ridiculous.
这是你的生日 这是你的派对
Okay, this is your birthday, this is your party.
我们得让他们知道实情
I say we just put them all together
如果他们不接受 谁在乎呢?
If they can't deal with it, who cares?
我在乎      那才是最重要的
I do.        That's who.
你没事吧?
Look, are you gonna be okay?
我真的没有选择 我得往好的方面去想
Well I have to be.I don't really have a choice.I mean, I can look at the bright side.
我有两个生日派对和两个生日蛋糕
I get two birthday parties and two birthday cakes.
事实上有一个是生日果馅饼
Well, actually just one birthday flan.
什么?      它是传统墨西哥馅饼甜点
What?        It's a traditional Mexican custard dessert.
去问摩妮卡 她负责食物 我不能...
Look, talk to Monica.She's on the food committee. I can't...
乔伊 有个女孩走向我 她说"我要你 丹尼斯"
Joe Joe, hey, some girl just walked up to me and said"I want you,Dennis"
然后把她的舌头伸进我的喉咙里
and stuck her tongue down my throat.
我爱这个派对      太棒了!
I love this party.        great!
排球机智问答      排球?
Quick volleyball question.        Volleyball?
我们在你房里搭了一个球场
Yeah, we set up a court in your room.
你不喜欢那盏灰色的灯吧?
Uh,you didn't like that gray lamp, did you?
有个女人将舌头伸进我的喉咙里
Joey, a woman just stuck her tongue down my throat.
我根本没在听你说话
I'm not even listening to you.
丹尼斯      她在叫我
Dennis.        Okay,that's me.
甜心 你能去陪爸爸吗? 我得跟我妈妈聊一会
Listen, ahem, honey, can you keep Dad occupied? I'm gonna go talk to Mom for a while.
好吧 我该说些什么?
Okay, do you have any ideas for any openers?
千万别提 "我正在跟你女儿上床"
Uh,let's just stay clear of "I'm the guy that's doing your daughter"
你应该就会没事
and you should be okay.
大家每人拿一张纸出来
Okay, people,I want you to take a piece of paper
来吧 写下你们最丢脸的事
you go. And write down your most embarrassing memory.
请大家不用麦克笔时一定要将笔帽盖上
And I do ask that when you're not using the markers...you put the caps back on them...
因为它们会干掉
because they will dry out.
你好 葛林医生
Hi Dr. Green.
血管外科手术怎么样了?
So how's everything in the, uh...
还好玩吧?
vascular surgery game?
那不是游戏 罗斯 今天有个女人死在手术台上了
It's not a game, Ross.A woman died on my table today.
我很遗憾
I'm sorry.
看 这就是我工作上的好处
See, that's the good thing about my job.
我工作台上的恐龙早就死了
All the dinosaurs on my table are already dead.
大伙们 我不想嗦了...
Listen, you guys, urn, I don't mean to be a pain about this...
但我发现有些人只是随意盖上
but, urn, I've noticed that some of you are just placing them on.
你们得用力压笔帽...
You want to push the caps...
直到听见"咔"的一声
until you hear them click.
阿甘 你要去哪里?
Gunther. Where are you going?
我想或许...
I, uh, was sort of thinking about maybe...
不 你不能走 这很好玩
No,No, you can't go. No, this is fun.
我们才刚刚开始 拿去 这是你的马克笔
Come on, come on, we're just getting started.Here's your marker
听着 你想走的话快点走
Listen, if you want to go, just go.
不 她还会吼我的
No. She'll yell at me again.
好吧 我能把你弄出去      什么?
All right,ahem, I can get you out.        What?
嘘~
Shh.
一分钟后我会分散她的注意力
In a minute, I'm gonna create a diversion.
你得趁乱走出去 千万别回头
When I do, walk quickly to the door and don't look back.
我想喝一杯      我去帮你拿酒
I think I need a drink.        Oh, I'll get it for you.
你要喝什么?      威士忌
What do you want?        Scotch.
我会很快拿着加冰威士忌回来的
All right, I'll be back in 10 seconds with your Scotch on the rocks in a glass.
纯的      加冰的      不 不 不
Neat.        Cool.        No, no, no.
我是说我要纯的不加冰块的
Neat, as in no rocks.
我知道了
Heh. I know.
罗斯 你跑到哪里去了?      你好
Oh, hello, Ross. Now, where have you been?        Hi
我在厕所里
Uh, I have been in the bathroom.
我得将鲑鱼慕斯吐出来
Ahem. Stay clear of the salmon mousse.
纯威士忌
Oh. Scotch neat.
瑞秋的爸爸也喝那个
You know, that's Rachel's father's drink.
我也是 那很酷吧?
Mine too. Isn't that neat?
纯威士忌
Scotch neat.
失陪一下
Would you excuse me?
喂 喂
Hey,Hey.
你要溜到哪里去 先生?
Where are you sneaking off to, mister? Heh.
烟放外套里了 我去拿
I'm getting my cigarettes out of my jacket.
别去      "别去"什么意思?
No.        No? What do you mean "no"?
不行 因为那是准备区
No. urn, see, because that's the staging area.
你去那里去会毁了你对派对的幻想的
You go in there, it'll ruin the whole illusion of the party.
对 拿着你的威士忌回去...
Yeah, I think, you take your Scotch back in there...
我去帮你拿烟
and I will get your cigarettes for you, sir.
也帮我拿眼镜来      没问题
And get my glasses too.        All righty-roo.
我第一次那么说竟然是在这种情况下
What a great moment to say that for the first time.
好吧 第一个人最丢脸回忆是
Okay, the first persons most embarrassing memory is
"摩妮卡 你的派对烂透了"
"Monica,your party sucks."
太有趣了
All right. Very funny.
天哪 有人忘了用杯垫吗?
Oh, no. Ooh. Did someone forget to use a coaster?
什么?
What?
我什么都没看到
I don't see anything.
好吧 我又看到水纹了
Great, I’m seeing water rings again.
罗斯 那是谁的眼镜?
Ross, whose glasses are those?
是我的
Mine.
你戴两用眼镜?
You wear bifocals?
嗯哼
Mm-hm.
我的眼睛有些问题所以我需要...
I have a condition apparently...that I require...
戴两用眼镜
two different sets of focals.
你知道我丈夫也有那种眼镜吗?
Do you know my husband has glasses just like that?
不知道      那种镜框很普遍
no        Well, those are very popular frames.
尼尔赛达卡也戴这种镜框
Neil Sedaka wears them.
听说你让我们出去
I hear you can get people out of here.
瑞秋      嗯?
Rachel?        Yeah?
你没告诉我你男朋友会抽烟
You didn't tell me your boyfriend smokes.
对 他烟瘾非常重
Yeah, like a chimney.
大烟枪
Big smoker
超级大烟枪
Big, big smoker.
事实上我要去走廊点燃这个坏小子
In fact,I'm gonna go out into the hallway and fire up this bad boy.
你戴我的眼镜?
Are you wearing my glasses?
是的
Yes.
我只是想帮你暖一下耳垫
I was just warming up the earpieces for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
那是我的烟吗?
Is that one of my cigarettes?
对
Yeah.
没错 我只是想帮你润润烟屁股
Yes, it is. I was just moistening the tip.
好吧 她要去倒垃圾 我能把你们弄出去
Okay, okay. She's taking the trash out, so I can get you out of here.
但你们得快离开 她随时都会回来
But it has to be now. She'll be back any minute.
我的朋友维克多怎么办?
What about my friend Victor?
只能你们三个 再多她一定会起疑
No, only the three of you. Any more than that and she'll get suspicious.
好吧 我去拿外套      没时间了
All right. Let me just get my coat.        There isn't time.
别带任何东西 隔壁的人会照顾你们
Just leave everything. They'll take care of you next door
他们真的有啤酒?
Is it true they have beer?
你们听到的事都是真的
Everything you've heard is true.
你们能不能小声点?
Could you guys please try and keep it down?
我们要开始玩惊异大巡航
We're trying to start a Boggle tournament.
你 还有你
You. And you.
你们应该在我的派对上 还有阿甘
You're supposed to be at my party. And Gunther.
你们在这里做什么?
What are you doing here?
呃...
Urn...
欢迎光临...
Hey, welcome to the fo...
菲比?
Phoebe?
好吧 对不起 但这些人需要我
All right, I'm sorry. But these people needed me.
他们努力工作了一星期 今天是周六夜
You know, they work hard all week. It's Saturday night.
他们需要狂欢 去吧
They deserve to have a little fun. Go.
我的派对很有趣 它比较安静 没那么好玩
You know, my party is fun.I mean, maybe it's a little quieter less obvious sort of fun.
如果大家愿意给它一个机会 它非常...
But, you know, if people would just give it a chance, it's...
你要我去看心理医生?      甜心 你明显有问题
You want me to see a therapist?        Sweetheart, you obviously have a problem.
你选的男朋友跟你爸是一个模子印出来的
You've chosen a boyfriend exactly like your father.
妈妈 你知道么? 好吧 我会去预约
Okay, Mom, you know what? Fine. I'll make an appointment.
但我得走了 我还有事要做
Okay? But you know what? Right now, I gotta go. I gotta go do a thing.
你知道你妈花一千二买盆栽的事吗?
Did you know your mother spent $1200 on bonsai trees?
我觉得自己被绑得喘不过气
I felt like Gulliver around that place.
爸爸 爸爸 我真的很想听你说 但我还有事要做
Daddy, Daddy I really want to hear more about this,i really do, but I just have to do,uh,some stuff.
我非常努力的经营婚姻
You work and you work and you work at a marriage...
但他只在乎他的笨船
but all he cares about is his stupid boat.
我非常努力地将船弄好
You work and you work and you work on a boat.
他老是嘲笑我的陶艺课
He always ridiculed my pottery classes.
帮它打光上漆
And you sand it and you varnish it.
我用尽所有办法 他还是用马克杯喝东西
But when all is said and done, he still drinks out of the mugs.
有一晚是她的瑜如课 跟"麦迪逊之桥"
One night of her yoga and her Bridges of Madison County...
威士忌 香烟...      盆栽 吉娃娃...
Scotch, cigarettes...        Bonsais, the Chihuahua...
我只做了三星期的心理治疗 但...
I've only been in therapy three weeks now but...
她要一半的船做什么?
What's the hell does she want with half a boat?
好吧 你当上衣 我当皮肤
Okay, okay, okay, you can be shirts and I'll be skins.
我可以当皮肤
I'll be skins.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吧 老虎?
How you holding up there, tiger?
抱歉 我爸妈离婚时 很多人叫我老虎
Oh. Sorry. When my parents were getting divorced, I got a lot of "tigers."
也有人叫我冠军 老大跟小子
Ahem. I got a lot of "champs" "chiefs" "sports"
有一个人叫我州长
Ahem. I even got a "governor"
这就是我的生活 对吧? 这就是我未来的人生
This is it,isn't it? I mean, this is what my life is gonna be like.
我妈在那里 我爸在那里 感恩节 圣诞节
My mom there, my dad there.Thanksgiving, Christmas.
她拿到房子 他住公寓 我妹妹会用藤制品装饰它
She gets the house, he's in some condo my sister's gonna decorate with wicker.
钱德 你是怎么撑过来的?
Chandler, how did you get through this?
我做了精心设计的心理治疗 治疗我的否认心态
Well, I relied on a carefully regimented program...of denial...
跟尿床问题
and wetting the bed.
我只是...感觉真的好怪
You know, I just...It's so weird.
我在那里听他们责备彼此
I mean, I was in there just listening to them bitch about each other.
脑袋里只想到独立纪念日
All I kept thinking about was the Fourth of July.
因为那让你想起我们的开国元老如何责备彼此?
Because it reminded you of the way...our forefathers used to bitch at each other?
他们吵架的原因就是
It's just this thing.
每年我们会坐我爸的船出海看烟火
Every year we would go out on my dads boat and watch the fireworks.
妈非常讨厌那么做 因为海风会将她的头发吹乱
Mom always hated it because the ocean air made her hair all big.
我妹妹吉儿会趴在船边吐
My sister Jill would be throwing up over the side...
爸很生气因为没有人帮他
and my dad would be upset because nobody was helping.
我们真的去帮他时 他会骂我们做错了
And then when we did help, he would scream at us for doing it wrong.
但开始施放烟火后大家会闭嘴
But then when the fireworks started, everybody just shut up.
因为真的很冷
You know, and it'd get really cold.
我们会一起窝在毯子里
And we'd all just sort of smoosh under this one blanket.
没有人想过要多带一条毯子
It never occurred to anybody to bring another one.
现在...
And now it's...
我知道
Yeah I know.
谢谢你们的光临 希望你们玩得开心
Thanks for coming. I hope you had fun.
好吧 我得回去了 我把我的十个动词放在桌上了
All right, Monica, dear I'm gonna hit the road. Now, I've left my 10 verbs on the table.
一定要把完成的诗寄给我
Yes, and you be sure and send me that finished poem.
我会的 很高兴你来了      好吧 亲爱的
Okay, will do. So glad you came.        All right, dear.
我看到瑞秋在走廊上      我去看看
I think I saw Rachel out in the hall.        Okay, let me go check.
好的
Oh, all right.
你妈要跟你道别      噢 好
Your mom wants to say goodbye.        Oh, okay.
生日快乐 甜心
Happy birthday, sweetie.
好
Okay.
乔伊 好好开车
Joey Uh, you drive safe.
好      罗斯 你在做什么?
Okay.        What are you doing?
我准备要去滑水
I'm getting ready for the water skiing.
好吧 再抱一次 快点
Okay, big hug. One more. Come on.
你好吗?
How are you?
你要去哪里?      拿我的外套
Dr. Green. Where are you going?        To get my coat.
别 别 别 我们去帮你拿
No, no, no. We'll get that for you.
好吧 我可以自己去拿外套
All right, all right. I can get my own coat.
抱歉 我们吃果馅饼兴奋过头了
Sorry, we're on a major flan high.
不 你不该在这里
Oh, no. No, you're not supposed to be here.
这里是准备区 这是不对的 你应该离开
This is the staging area. It's all wrong. You should leave.
你得离开这里
Ha, ha. You know, just get out.
或许你想来杯薄荷甜酒
Or perhaps you'd like acremede menthe.
我得回我的别墅去 谢谢
I have to be heading toward my chateau. Thank you.
我想我们要回走廊了
All right, well then I guess we're going back into the hallway again.
谢谢你赶过来 葛林太太
Thanks for coming, Mrs. Green.
好吧
Okay.
保重
You take care.
你们这些孩子
Oh, you kids.
好了
Well
这是多年来我参加过最棒的派对
This is the best party I've been to in years.
谢谢
Thank you.
大伙们 果馅饼时间到了
Okay, everybody, it's time for flan.
准备大尝好吃的果冻
Yep. Get ready for the gelatinous fun.
看起来很像严重感染时涂的药膏
Kind of looks like that stuff you get when you get a bad infection.
够了
Okay, thats enough.
瑞秋 许个特别的果馅饼愿望
Okay, Rachel, make a special flan wish.
我许好了
Okay, I've got one.
小心
Heads up.
那些愿望几乎都无法成真
Wow. Those things almost never come true.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧